[EP01]
Aren't you happy being my wife?
What else do you want?
Kill me.
Why did I dream of him again?
I always have some strange dreams.
Director said
the surgical procedure was fine.
The complications were unexpected.
He wants you to withdraw your resignation.
The department is still waiting for you.
I know it's a big blow to you
to face the death of a patient for the first time.
But as the attending doctor of Bed Two,
you've done your best.
You should think twice about resigning.
Then I may
never be a doctor again.
[Emergency call.]
[Cardiac Surgery Department is receiving a severely injured patient.]
with a blood loss of over 1500cc.
Doctors from surgery and anesthesia,
please go to the operating room on the third floor.
Hurry up.
Go.
This way.
Be careful.
What else do you know?
It was Chu Nanfeng.
He told me that Commander Ling was dead.
I don't know anything else.
Go back and tell Shen Family
their young master drank too much today.
He was dead when he was sent to the hospital.
Yes.
Ling Shenxing,
my sister is pregnant with your brother.
How dare you do this to me?
You deserve to die.
What Shen Family's young master said
is not entirely wrong.
The news in the city is the same as what we know.
Commander Ling is missing.
Father mentioned the Su Family many times in his letter.
The disappearance of my father is related to the Su Family.
The head of the Su Family is missing.
Our people are trying to find him.
We don't know
if other families are involved in this.
There's one more thing.
Miss Su jumped into a well.
Does Old Madam Su mean
she's dead?
She means
don't make a fuss.
Just deal with it today.
Do you want to see Miss Su?
After all, she's your wife.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Miss.
My lady.
Chayu.
My lady, I'm your personal maid, Hongxiu.
My lady.
Chayu.
Where is this place?
What's going on?
My daughter.
Who are you?
It's all Ling's fault that you are like this.
I'll fight to the death
to get justice
for you.
The Su family sells illegal drugs.
Arrest the head of the Su family
and put him in prison.
Young Marshal, spare me.
[The man in the corridor.]
[Who are you?]
My Lady,
he is your husband.
Ling Shenxing.
Mr. Ling.
[Ling Shenxing.]
[Isn't this the name of the male lead]
[in the novel I listened to?]
[Su Muwan is the name of the female lead.]
[And I'm Su Muwan now.]
[So I've traveled into the book.]
Cousin.
Watch out.
She came back from the dead.
She's not human, she's a demon.
What tricks are you playing now, Miss Su?
Suicide?
Amnesia?
Or
are you involved
in the Su family's affairs?
[Oh, no.]
[Ling Shenxing in the book]
[hates Su Muwan the most.]
[What should I do now?]
Young Marshal,
my daughter knows nothing.
The disappearance of Commander Ling
has nothing to do with us.
My belly hurts.
Second Concubine.
Doctor.
What's wrong with you?
Call the doctor.
Go.
Master, run.
Master.
Master Su.
I want to go back.
Go back?
Yes.
Die.
Am I able to go back after I die?
Kill me.
What do you want to do?
Or
this is a play
you and your father are acting.
I can finally go back.
It seems that Miss Su didn't drown to death
last time.
This time it's because her heart
is different from others.
It's on the right side.
So,
there is no life-threatening.
Just rest well,
and she'll be fine.
Fuyuan.
Yes.
Send the doctor off,
and boil the medicine for Second Concubine.
Yes, Madam.
Fortunately,
your unborn brother is fine.
Now in the city,
only the news of your father's disappearance
is spreading wildly.
You...
Nonsense!
Father just wrote to me.
He will return soon.
That's good.
The Sus are found to have illegal drugs.
What are you going to do with them?
Illegal drugs?
It can cause death.
Mr. Su is dead.
If Su Muwan didn't know about it,
the Lings
can give her a job.
Hmph.
You are so kind.
Do you think Su Muwan
doesn't know her heart is on the right side?
She faked her death.
She had an affair with Chu Nanfeng,
which caused a sensation in the city.
She didn't care about your face at all.
Take this opportunity
to divorce her.
You,
her,
should all return to their proper places
and get back on track.
Madam.
Young Marshal, please spare me.
and Jinrou